時は戦国、乱世の時代。
からくり人の住むジパング国では群雄割拠して合戦に明け暮れ、
からくり武芸者たちも勝利と栄光を目指してしのぎを削っていた。
そしていま、からくり武芸者ナンバー１を目指す、とてつもないヒーローが誕生した！
ムサシ、見参でござるだス！
からくり剣豪伝ムサシロード
男はいつでも　世界の真ん中で
いちばん　強くなる日を
AH! AH! 夢見て
心の刃　大空にふりかざし
冒険の旅の　幕を開ける
ジパング国を　さすらう剣豪
その名　からくりびと　ムサシ
GO! FIGHT!
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　昨日よりも　今日　強い
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
明日は　輝くぞ
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　思い切りと　静けさと
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
みけんが　きらめいた　ムサシ！！
여행 도중 쓰잘데기없는 일로 싸운 무사시와 코지로.
Musashi and Kojirō fought over something so absurd.
그리고 놀랍게도 무사시가 승리했다.
And surprisingly, Musashi won.
거기에 돌연 나타난 오츠루와 미야모토 마을 사람들.
Otsuru and people of Miyamoto village suddenly appeared.
즐거운 밤을 보낸 무사시였지만 결국엔 너구리에게 속았을 뿐이었다.
Musashi spent a fun night, but he was simply fooled by some raccoons.
나왔다 수수께끼의
육도마왕이오
He Appeared!
Mysterious Rikudomaoh
전부 끝났는가.
Is everything over?
음?
Hm?
즉시 수용해라.
Take him in right now.
한조 님. 우리 메가톤 성에 오신 걸 환영합니다.
Mr. Hanzō. Welcome to our Megaton Castle.
누구냐?
Who's there?
나는 도쿠간류.
I am Dokuganryu.
도쿠간류.
Dokuganryu.
날 어쩔 셈이냐.
What are you going to do with me?
도쿠간류
Dokuganryu
육도마왕님이 부르신다.
Lord Rikudomaoh is waiting.
육도마왕? 누구냐!
Rikudomaoh? Who's that?!
흥. 곧 알게 된다. 일단 상처부터.
You'll figure it out soon. We'll take care of your wounds first.
그 쯤, 무사시는 온천에서 피로를 팍 풀고 있었다.
Meanwhile, Musashi was taking an extraordinary rest at a hot spring.
노천탕에 들어가서 먹는 온천만두 최고! 잘 먹겠소!
Eating hot spring dumplings in an open air bath is best-dasu! Thank you for the meal-dasu!
무사시, 서둘러!
Musashi, hurry up!
어라라라, 뭔 짓이오!
Hey, what are you doing-dasu?!
에도토피아에서 무예대회이오.
A martial arts competition at Edotopia-dasu!
법령의 지팡구 무예 대회를 개최한다. 전국의 무예가 제군, 꼭 참가 부탁한다. 상품도 가득 준비해 놓고 기다리겠다.
I'm holding the annual Jipangu Martial Arts Competition.
All the martial artists in this country, don't miss out this opportunity. I also prepared numerous prizes.
오, 타오르오! 이번에야말로 지팡 제일의 영광으로 빛나겠소!
This makes me burn-dasu! I'll shine with the glory of the number one of Jipangu-dasu!
그런 곳에서 꾸물대지 말고 서둘러 항구로 가야 해!
Don't take too much time there; we have to go the port!
배가 기다린다!
A ship is waiting for us!
그, 그런 건 빨리 말해 주시오!
Y- you could have told me that earlier-dasu!
출항!
Now leaving port!
기다려!
Wait for me!
아, 지라이얀! 저 녀석도 태워 주시오!
Oh, Jiraiyan! Let him in, too-dasu!
알겠습니다!
Understood!
아, 멋져!
That was cool!
꽤 하오, 지라이얀!
You're good-dasu, Jiraiyan!
아니, 땀난다, 땀나!
That made me sweat!
지라이얀도 무예 대회에 나가오?
Are you joining the martial arts competition too-dasu?
응. 용서해 준다면 꼭 카라쿠리 무예가로서 정정당당히 승부하고 싶다.
Yes. If people forgive me, then I'd like to have a fair and square match as a Karakuri martial artist.
좋소, 지라이얀! 힘내시오!
Great, Jiraiyan! Do your best-dasu!
이런 게 바닷속을 돌아다닐 줄이야. 육도마왕이라는 놈의 힘이라면 어쩌면 지팡구국을 뒤엎을 수 있을 터.
A thing like this in the deep sea? Maybe the power of that Rikudomaoh would be enough to turn over Jipangu State.
두고 볼 가치가 있다.
It worths to observe for now.
뭔 일입니까!
What's wrong?!
괴물이야! 봐봐!
A monster! Look!
크오! 고래이오?
It's big-dasu! Is it a whale-dasu?
고래하고는 달라요.
It's different from whales.
어?
Huh?
세토 내해에서 요즘 뜨는 소문의 괴물입니다.
It's a recent rumored monster of Seto Inland Sea.
괴물입니까?
A monster?
정체는 불명이지만, 가끔은 큰 배도 집어삼킨다고 합니다.
Its identitiy is unknown, but it is sometimes told to swallow up a huge ship.
호? 잡아서 정체를 보고 싶네.
I want to catch one and see what it is.
변함없이 덜렁말 공주네...
She's a shrew as always...
지라이얀!
Jiraiyan!
아, 이건 실례했습니다.
Oh, excuse me.
이번에 발견하면 내가 잡아서...
When it shows up again, I'll catch it and...
아! 어서어서 저리 가! 기분 나빠!
Hey! Get this off me right now! That's horrible!
센히메 님! 단지 줄입니다.
Senhime! It's just a rope.
센짱의 배짱이란 것도 대단한 게 아니오!
Sen-chan's guts isn't something great-dasu!
무사시!
Musashi!
아, 봐주시오!
Forgive me-dasu!
멈춰라, 무사시!
Stop right there, Musashi!
싫소!
No way-dasu!
날려버리겠어!
I'll throw you away!
싫소!
No way-dasu!
한조 님이구나.
You must be Mr. Hanzō.
그렇지. 자, 너희들은?
Right. And you people?
나는 신겐.
I am Shingen.
신겐
Shingen
켄신
Kenshin
나는 켄신.
I am Kenshin.
나를 이런 곳에 데려와서 어쩔 생각이냐.
What made you call me to a place like this?
우리는 지팡국을 적으로 싸운 한조 님의 힘을 높이 평가하여.
We rate your power high, Mr. Hanzō, for fighting against Jipangu State for a long time.
이 자들, 평범내기가 아니군. 잠시 태도를 시험해 볼까.
These people aren't ordinary people. Let me test your moves...
걱정할 필요 없다.
No need to worry.
역시 한조 님. 현명하시다.
Great, Mr. Hanzō. You are bright.
한조던가. 내가 육도마왕이다.
You must be Hanzō. I am Rikudomaoh.
육도마왕.
Rikudomaoh.
도쿠가와를 쓰러트리고 내가 바라는 평화에서 서민에게 행복을 주는 지팡구국 건설에 함께 하지 않겠는가.
Wouldn't you like to join me, to take Tokugawa down and build Jipangu State that I want,
where commoners can find happiness in peace?
육도마왕이던가. 이 나를 네 부하로 하고 싶다는 말인가?
You must be Rikudomaoh. You want me to become your subordinate?
그건 기가 막히는구나! 누군진 모르겠지만 이 한조, 사람 명령을 듣는 고분고분한 성격이 아니다.
How grateful! Whoever you are, I, Hanzō, do not obediently follow orders.
실례하겠다.
Now excuse me.
한조. 다시 한번 묻겠다. 함께할 생각 없나.
Hanzō. Let me ask you again. Wouldn't you like to join me?
아, 알겠다! 협력하겠다!
I- I understand! I'll join!
내게 거역할 때, 그 팔찌는 그 쪽의 명을 앗아갈 것이다.
When you disobey me, that ring will take your life.
그러나 내 명령에 따를 때, 그것은 불사신의 갑옷이 될 것이다.
But when you do obey me, that will become an invulnerable armor.
이 갑옷이!
This armor!
조조의 갑옷. 그것을 입으면 불사신이 된다.
(sousou: Japanese pronunciation of Chinese chancellor Cao Cao)
Sousou Armor. With that, you will be invulnerable.
불사신의 갑옷?
Invulnerable armor?
육도마왕. 대체 어떠한 놈인가.
Rikudomaoh. What can this guy do?
에도토피아는 오랜만이오!
It's been a while since I've been in Edotopia-dasu!
오랜만의 번화함!
This liveliness is great!
센히메 님을 무사하게 안내할 수 있어서 다행이었습니다.
It was my pleasure to be able to protect Senhime without mishap.
자, 자, 지팡구 무예 대회는 드디어 내일! 지난번의 우승자는 주베였지만, 새 우승자가 태어나는가!
Jipangu Martial Arts Competition is tomorrow at last! Jūbee was the champion last time; will someone else win this time?!
예상이 나와 있습니다! 오세요, 오세요!
We have expectations and explanations! Come and get your copy!
아, 하나 주시오!
Gimme one-dasu!
감사합니다!
Thank you!
올해의 우승은 미야모토 마을의 무사시이오.
This year's champion will be Musashi from Miyamoto village-dasu.
크게 될 놈이군.
What a futuristic guy.
어때, 나와 있어, 무사시?
Can you find your name on it, Musashi?
오, 있다, 있어! 인기 제일은 츠바메가에시의 코지로. 해냈구나, 코지로!
Hey, there you are! The number one of popularity is Kojirō of Tsubamegaeshi. You did it, Kojirō!
그런! 인기라면 예능인에게는 당연히 있습니다.
(bu"gei": Martial Arts, "gei"noujin: people with art capabilities; performer; celebrity)
Of course! Performers are supposed to be popular.
실력 제일은 역시 주베구나. 그래, 당연하네!
The number one of abilities is Jūbee, of curse. I knew it!
화려함 제일은 우시와카.
The number one of splendor is Ushiwaka.
수긍이 가네.
I can agree with that.
저, 저, 내 이름은 없소?
Hey, is my name not on there-dasu?
어? 잠깐 보자. 힘 제일은 벤케이. 다크 호스는 지라이얀.
Hm? Let me see. Powered no.1 is Benkei. Dark Horse is Jiraiyan.
있다, 있다! 미야모토 마을의 무사시 제일!
Here you are! Musashi from Miyamoto village is number one at-!
어라? 어디, 어디이오?
Huh? Where, where-dasu?
봐! 생뚱맞은 웃음거리 제일이 무사시래!
Look! The number one stupid comedian is Musashi!
웃음거리
Comedian
(와판: 에도 시대에 찰흙에 새겨 기와처럼 구운 판에 인쇄한 속보 기사판)
(Tile block print: kawaraban; newsflash newspaper made of roofing tiles in Edo period)
와판에 이름이 적혀있는 것만으로도 대단한 거야, 무사시.
Having your name written on the tile block print itself is something great, Musashi.
왜 내가 웃음거리 제일이오!
Why am I the 1st of comedian-dasu?!
아무래도 상관없지만 접수만은 똑바로 해라. 작년의 바보를 잊지 마라.
I don't care, but at least get your application done properly. Do not forget last year's idiot.
말 안 해도 알고 있소!
You don't have to remind me that-dasu!
부탁하오.
I'm participating-dasu!
오, 너 기합 들어갔구나!
Oh, you're with some spirit!
좋아, 여기에 출신지, 유파, 이름을 적어라.
Good. Write where you're from, your school, and your name on here.
알겠소!
Got it-dasu!
출신은 미야모토 마을.
I'm from Miyamoto village.
유파는 이천일류.
My school is Nitenichiryu.
이름은 무사시.
My name is Musashi.
이게 네 번호다.
This is your number.
땡큐이오.
Thank you-dasu.
오, 이건 대단하오! 봐 보시오, 센짱!
This is awesome-dasu! Look at this, Sen-chan!
무사시 일번!
Musashi, the first!
내가 일번이오! 즉 우승이오!
I'm the first! Meaning that I win-dasu!
잘 봐라, 무사시.
Take a look again, Musashi.
이건 무사시 일번이 되지 못함. 이라고 읽는 거야.
This is how you read it: Musashi, the first in reverse.
그런 거 상관 없잖아! 실력이야! 힘내, 뭇사ㅣ!
That doesn't matter! Your ability is what's important here! Go for it, Musashi!
그럼 나, 할아버지 있는 곳에 갈 테니까!
Then, I'm going to where my grandpa is!
내일 보자!
See you tomorrow!
아, 문까지 배웅해 드리겠습니다.
Let me take you to the door.
왠지 눈물나오오.
It's making me sad-dasu.
단고이오!
Dangos-dasu!
여전히 단고는 참 좋아하네, 무사시 씨?
You still like dangos very much, Mr. Musashi!
어, 어라, 이 목소리!
H- huh? This voice!
무사시 씨?
Mr. Musashi?
오츠루!
Otsuru!
오츠루도 에도토피아로 나와 있었소!
You were at Edotopia, too-dasu!
그래.
Right.
무사시 씨가 지팡구 무예 대회에 분명 올 거라고 생각해서 여기서 일하면서 기다렸어.
I knew you were going to come to Jipangu Martial Arts Competition, so I waited here and worked meanwhile that!
오츠루하고 만나서, 나 용기 백배이오!
My courage is now 100 times as I met Otsuru-dasu!
사실은 단고 덕분이지?
I know that it's actually because of dangos!
아니, 아니오!
No, it isn't-dasu!
정말?
Really?
생략하오!
No comment!
오츠루, 지금 어디에 살고 있소?
Otsuru, where are you living at now-dasu?
지금, 나는...
I'm now at...
자, 잔뜩 먹어라!
Stuff your stomach here!
무사시 씨의 우승을 미리 축하하는 거야!
This is a pre-celebration for your championship, Mr. Musashi!
제니가탄 두목, 아카네 씨, 나 기쁘오! 이런 진수성찬은 태어나서 처음이오!
Boss Zenigatan and Ms. Akane, I'm happy-dasu! I never had a feast like this-dasu!
이 붕어, 이 조림, 아카네 씨가 구운 거야. 먹어. 아-
Ms. Akane made this boiled carp. Eat! Ah-
어디어디, 오, 맛있소!
Let me taste! Oh, that's delicious-dasu!
무사시 씨, 정말 잔뜩 먹네!
That Mr. Musashi really is stuffing!
무사시가 하도 기뻐서 어찌할 줄 모르고 폭식하고 있을 그 때.
Meanwhile Musashi's at ecstasy and gorging...
세토 내해에 거대한 괴물이 출현했다.
A humongous monster appeared at Seto Inland Sea.
질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
메가톤성 탑승에게 전한다. 지금부터 미야코 팔레스를 공격.
To everyone on Megaton Castle. We're now attacking Miyako Palace.
총원 해치에 붙어라!
Everyone, stick to nearest hatches!
한조. 즉시 중부대를 모아서 궁궐 팔레스를 덮쳐, 국왕의 증표인 삼중의 신기를 빼앗아 와라.
Hanzō. Gather a serious group of troop,
make a raid upon the imperial palace, and take the Three Sacred Treasures, the certificates of the king.
삼종의 신기?
The Three Sacred Treasures?
(보통 방패가 아닌 거울로 함)
(Usually it's mirror, not shield)
성스러운 양날검과 방패, 그리고 곡옥이야말로 지팡국의 왕의 증거다.
Sacred sword, shield, and round jewel are the certificates of king.
그럼 육도마왕이 바라는 건 국왕의 자리를 채어서 지팡구국의 왕이 되는 것인가.
Then the desire of Rikudomaoh must be taking the seat of the king and become the king of Jipangu State.
거기까지 알 필요는 없다.
You do not have to know that much.
뭐?!
What?!
이 명령에 따르지 않으면 네 팔의 팔찌가 폭발해서 갈갈이 찢어질 것을...
Do not forget that when you don't follow that order, the ring on your arm will explode and you will be...
잊지 마라.
ripped into pieces.
무, 무슨!
N- no way!
쇼토쿠, 뭔 일이냐.
Shotoku, what is it?
국왕 전하, 즉시 피난을!
Your Highness, please take immediate refuge!
더 서두르십시오!
Hurry up more!
전하!
Your Highness!
삼종의 신기, 이 한조가 가져가겠다.
I, Hanzō, will take that Three Sacred Treasures.
얼척이 없군. 국왕 전하께 칼을 향하다니 용서할 수 없다!
How impolite of you! Directing your sword towards the Highness is unforgivable!
처벌해 주겠다!
You will be punished!
됐는가?
Did it work?
무슨, 불사신이냐!
Is he immortal?!
국왕을 망자로 만들고 삼종의 신기를 가져가면 일석이조.
Making the king into a dead person and taking the Three Sacred Treasures is just like killing two birds with one stone.
제기랄! 어디로 사라졌냐!
Damn! Where did they disappear to?!
쇼토쿠, 궁전이...
Shotoku. The palace...
무념입니다, 국왕 전하!
Very regretful, your Highness!
국왕을 놓치고, 신기를 둘밖에 손에 못 넣었구나.
You let the king run away, and took only two treasures.
면목 없다.
I'm ashamed.
뭐, 됐다. 무사히 달아났다면 의지하고 갈 곳은 에도토피아.
Well, that already happened. If he successfully ran away, then he must be heading to Edotopia.
제너럴 이에야스.
General Ieyasu.
방법이 있지. 거기에 에도토피아도 쳐부수면 일석이조.
There's a way for everything. Destroying Edotopia too will be like killing two birds with one stone.
그거하고는 상관없이 드디어 무예가 제일을 가리는 대회가 시작되었다.
Nonetheless, the competition that will find out the number one martial artist has begun.
이천일류 무사시 님 대 간코류 간세키사이 님!
Mr. Musashi of Nitenichiryu versus Mr. Gansekisai of Gankoryu!
시작!
Start!
이도류라니 건방지구나. 정면 세로베기!
Using dual blade? How impertinent. Front Straight Down Cut!
이천일류, 가위치기!
Nitenichiryu: Crab Interpose!
내 것이오!
You're mine-dasu!
뭣이?!
What?!
졌다!
I lost!
아싸! 해냈소!
Yay! I did it-dasu!
비검 츠바메가에시!
Secret Sword Tsubamegaeshi!
코지로 님!
Mr. Kojirō!
이천일류 번개치기!
Nitenichiryu: Lightening Cut!
무사시는 순조롭게 2회전, 3회전으로 이겨 나가고 있었다. 그러나 코지로나 주베를 시작으로, 무사시의 라이벌도 지지 않았다.
Musashi was keeping to win and went to the 2nd and 3rd matches.
But his rivals, including Kojirō and Jūbee, weren't losing, too.
이야, 무사시 씨! 이번 여행으로 차이가 크나커졌어!
Mr. Musashi! Your last journey surely has made you heavily different!
나, 살쪘소?
Did I become fat-dasu?
그게 아니라, 강하고 늠름해졌다는 것!
No, it means that you become strong and gallant!
그런 것이었소!
That's what it meant-dasu!
많이 먹고 이번에야말로 지팡구 제일이 되어 주쇼!
Eat a lot, and become the number one of Jipangu for surely this time!
해내겠소! 꼭 우승해 보이겠소!
I'll do it-dasu! I'll be the champion for sure-dasu!
정말 덜렁댄다니까.
You're always so frivolous!
맞아!
Right!
서둘러라! 한시라도 빨리 에도토피아에 들어가야 한다!
Hurry! We have to enter Edotopia as soon as possible!
삼종의 신기의 하나, 성스러운 양손검을 놓쳤다?
You missed one of the Three Sacred Treasures, the sacred sword?
면목이 없습니다. 그렇지만 국왕의 목적지는 짐작이 갑니다.
I am deeply ashamed by this. But I have an estimation of the destination of the king.
에도토피아의 이에야스.
Ieyasu of Edotopia.
지금 에도토피아는 무예 대회로 축제 분위기입니다. 화공 작전에 절호의 기회입니다.
Edotopia is in a festive mood by a martial arts competition. This is the best chance to attack with fire.
피를 보는 것은 싫지만 목적을 위해서라면, 도쿠간류, 한조, 너희들에게 맡기겠다.
I do not like to see bloods, but for our objective, Dokuganryu and Hanzō, you will take care of this.
그러나 서민을 괴롭히면 안 된다.
But you must not harass the commoners.
예! 이에야스 놈을 쓰러트려, 성스러운 양손검을 꼭 손에 넣어 돌아오겠습니다.
Yessir! We will take Ieyasu down and claim the sacred sword before coming back.
자, 자, 오늘 새로 나온 와판입니다!
New tile block prints are now available!
잘생긴 코지로의 츠바메가에시에 무사시의 이도류의 비밀이 잔뜩!
All the secrets of handsome Kojirō's Tsubamegaeshi and Musashi's dual blades are here!
게다가 무엇보다도, 일단 무사시와 지라이얀의 대결입니다!
And most of all, we have Musashi vs. Jiraiyan first!
이건 구경거리입니다!
This will be spectacular!
무사시 씨. 지라이얀하고...
Mr. Musashi. With Jiraiyan...
지라이얀. 여기서 대결을 할 것이라고는 생각하지 않았소.
Jiraiyan. I never thought I'm going to face you here-dasu.
나는 무사시 덕분에 착실한 카라쿠리 무예가로 다시 일어섰다. 그럼 온 힘을 다해서 해 보자!
I stood up again as a honest Karakuri martial artist, thanks to you, Musashi. Now let's fight with all we got!
바라던 바이오!
Just as I wanted-dasu!
시작!
Start!
무사시 씨! 힘내!
Mr. Musashi! Go for it!
아, 오츠루, 멋진 모습 보여주겠소!
Right, Otsuru! I'll show my best-dasu!
빈틈이다!
Chink in the armor!
이천일류, 가위치기!
Nitenichiryu: Crab Interpose!
움직일 수가 없어!
I can't move!
졌다, 무사시!
I lost, Musashi!
무사시 님 승리! 준준결승전 진출!
Mr. Musashi wins! Advancing to semi-semi-finals!
지라이얀.
Jiraiyan.
무사시.
Musashi.
나, 졌어도 기뻐, 무사시.
I'm feeling happy even after being lost, Musashi.
어? 져서 기쁘오?
Huh? Are you happy because you lost-dasu?
그래. 한조의 부하였을 때에는 나쁜 세계에 있었지만, 함께 무예 대회의 영광의 장소에 설 수 있어서.
Yes. I was in an evil world when I was under Hanzō, but now I could stand on the honorable grounds of martial arts contest.
정정당당하게 싸워서 나도 기쁘오!
I'm happy too, since we fought fair and square-dasu!
고맙다, 무사시.
Thank you, Musashi.
지라이얀.
Jiraiyan.
무사시. 반드시 우승해 와라! 기도할 테니까!
Musashi! Be the champion! I'm praying for you!
나 힘내오!
I'll do my best-dasu!
나, 이번에야말로 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 되오!
I'm becoming the number one martial artist of Jipangu this time-dasu!
그래, 꼭!
Yes, you will!
그러면 나...
And after that, I...
응?
Yes?
아니, 아니...
No, no...
지금 이러고 있는 중에도 평화로운 에도토피아에 공포가 다가온다.
Even meanwhile he's doing this, a dread is approaching peaceful Edotopia.
무사시, 데이트 하고 있을 때가 아니다!
Musashi, it's not a time for you to have a date!
몸도 마음도 다잡고 가라! 싸워라!
Brace both your body and spirit, and go! Fight!
사내 무사시의 최고조의 순간이 다가온다.
(shounenba: the most important scene where the actor must not make mistake in acts like kabuki; do-or-die situation)
The climax of our man Musashi is near.
カラのポケットに　ツキが
飛び込むことも　あるさ
おっきな声で　笑えば
あしたには　朝が来る
無くすものなんか　何もないさ
やっちゃえ！イケイケ！
手ぶらは　強いぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
人生　てなもんさ　チャンスが　ほら
しっぽを振って　追ってくるぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
未来も　てなもんさ　あしたが　ほら
両手ひろげて　笑ってるぜ
무예 대회 준결승! 드디어 코지로하고 결판낼 때가 왔소.
Semi-finals of Martial Arts Competition! It's finally the time to settle up with Kojirō-dasu.
나, 지지 않소!
I won't lose-dasu!
그런데 국왕 전화를 쫒아 메가톤성이 에도토피아에 출현.
But chasing the Highness, Megaton Castle appeared at Edotopia.
이야, 대체 이런 놈하고 어떻게 싸워야 좋소?!
How can I possibly fight with something that huge-dasu?!
다음 이야기! 괴물! 메가톤성이오
Next story! Monster! Megaton Castle
질풍노도의 합체성이오!
It's the stormy Fusion Castle-dasu!
다음 이야기
괴물!
메가톤성이오
기대하세요!
Next Episode
A Monster!
Megaton Castle
Look forwards for it!